A Guide to the National Association of Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors, 1970-2000
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Correspondence (Box 89-93)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--1-19 March (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--20-31 March (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--April (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--1-15 May (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--16-31 May (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--June (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--July (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--August (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--1-10 September (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--11-30 September (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - 1986--Correspondence--October (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - 1986--Correspondence--November (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - 1986--Correspondence--December, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - 1986--Kansas Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors Association (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - 1986--Charlotte Chapman (1984-1986) (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - 1986--Stephen H. Kreimer (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - 1986--Franklin D. Lisnow (1982-1986) (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - 1986-1993--N. Kay Mattingly-Langlois (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - 1986--Adrea O. Sigler (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - 1987--Correspondence--January (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - 1987--Correspondence--February (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - 1987--Correspondence--1-9 March (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - 1987--Correspondence--10-19 March (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - 1987--Correspondence--20-31 March (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - 1987--Correspondence--1-15 April (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - 1987--Correspondence--16-30 April (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - 1987--Correspondence--1-11 May (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - 1987--Correspondence--12-20 May (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - 1987--Correspondence--21-31 May (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - 1987--Correspondence--1-8 June (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - 1987--Correspondence--9-30 June (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - 1987--Correspondence--July (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - 1987--Correspondence--August (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - 1987--Correspondence--September (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - 1987--Correspondence--October (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - 1987--Correspondence--November (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - 1987--Correspondence--December (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - 1987--Correspondence--n.d (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - 1987--Chris and Anne Fajardo (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - 1988--Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - 1989--Correspondence--January-September (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - 1989--Correspondence--October-December, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - 1990--Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - 1992--Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Committees (Box 94)
  - 1982-1985--Intra-governmental Affairs Committee (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - 1985--Ethics Committee (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - 1985--Impaired Counselor Committee (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - 1985--NAADAC Awards Committee (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - 1985--Personnel Committee (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - 1986--Legislative Committee (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - 1986--Nominations and Elections Committee (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - 1987--Nominations and Elections Committee (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Elections (Box 94)
  - 1982--Executive Committee--Biographies and photographs (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - 1982-1984--Regional vice-presidents (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - 1985--Election procedures (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - 1986--Election results (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - 1986--Resolution concerning balloting (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - 1987--Candidates (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - 1990--Election Ballots (Box 94, Folder 15)
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Membership (Box 94)
  - 1978-1980--Sustaining members (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - 1981--Membership survey form (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Handbooks, Manuals (Box 94)
  - 1980--NAAC procedural handbook and manual (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - 1986--Board of Directors meeting--Manual origins (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Awards (Box 94)
  - 1985--Counselor of the Year Award (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - 1986--Awards (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - 1987--Awards (Box 94, Folder 22)
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Miscellaneous (Box 94)
  - 1982--Legislation (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - 1986--50th anniversary script (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - 1986--Legislative Conference attendance (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - 1986--NAADAC Annual Conference--Official delegates (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - 1987--Benefit Policy and office information (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - 1987--Best of US Auction (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - 1987--Federal Employees Health Benefits Reform Act (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - 1987--Peer assistance (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - 1987--Speeches (Box 94, Folder 31)
- Executive Director's Files - Correspondence (Box 95)
  - 1977-1978--Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - 1977-1978--Doug Harton -Mel Schulstad correspondence (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - 1978--Doug Harton (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - 1978--WADACA--Eleanor Edelstein (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - 1978-September 1979--Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - 1979--Correspondence--October-December, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - 1980--Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - 1985--Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - 1989--Correspondence--January-August (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - 1989--Correspondence--September-December, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - 1990--Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - 1991--Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - 1992--Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - 1993--Correspondence--January-May (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - 1993--Correspondence--June-December, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - 1994--Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Executive Director's Files - Committees (Box 96-97)
  - 1978--Executive Committee (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - 1978--NIAAA Steering Committee (Box 96, Folder 2-3)
  - 1979--Executive Committee--24 February--Doug Harton (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - 1979--Executive Committee-Mel Schulstad (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - 1986--Peer Assistance Committee (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - 1988-1989, n.d.--Peer Assistance Committee (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - 1989--Committees (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - 1990-1991--Committees (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - 1991-1992--Committees (1991) (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - 1991-1992--Committees (1992) (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - 1991-1992--Committees--Budgets (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - 1992-1993--Committees (1992) (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - 1992-1993--Committees (1993) (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - 1993--Strategic Planning Committee (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - 1993-1994--Committees--Correspondence (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - 1993-1994--Committees--Budgets (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Executive Director's Files - Meetings, Conferences (Box 97-98)
  - 1977--Kansas City MO meeting--short and long term goals & attendance roster (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - 1977--Membership committee meeting (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - 1978--NAAC Executive Committee meeting--7-8 January (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - 1978--NAAC mailing labels for bulk shipments--February (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - 1978--Detroit meeting, by-laws, budget (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - 1978--Memphis mailing list--"extra" (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - 1978--Annual meeting--Memphis TN--Resolutions, correspondence, etc. (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - 1978--Message from Memphis (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - 1978--Memphis thank-you letters (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - 1979--NAAC Convention--Cincinnati OH--31 October-4 November (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - 1980--Annual meeting--Syracuse NY--30 July-4 August (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - 1994--Legislative Conference--February-March (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Executive Director's Files - Affiliates (Box 98)
  - 1975--NAACT (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - 1975-1978--Early affiliates of NAAC (NAADAC) (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - 1976--Topeka KS membership meeting--10-12 June (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - 1976--Hartford CT meeting--8-9 October (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - 1978--Affiliates and directors (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Executive Director's Files - Financial (Box 98)
  - 1975--Financial (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - 1977--NAAC 1978 budget & 1977 expenditures (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - 1978--appeal for money (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - 1979--Financial statements (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Executive Director's Files - Surveys (Box 98)
  - 1980--Counselor survey (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - 1992-1994--Peer assistance survey (Box 98, Folder 13-14)
- Executive Director's Files - Miscellaneous (Box 98)
  - 1975--By-laws (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - 1976-1977--Corporation papers for Virginia (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - 1978--NAAC and Southern Area Alcohol Education and Training Program Inc.--Payment for computer lists (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - 1978--NAAC response to states services contracts for manpower and training (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - 1978--NAAC Quarterly first issue, mailing lists, etc. (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - 1979--Manual (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - 1979--Annual report responses (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - 1980--Credentialing of alcoholism counselors (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - 1994--Leadership training (Box 98, Folder 23)
- NAADAC Foundation - Correspondence (Box 99)
  - 1989--Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - 1990--Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - 1992-1993--Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - 1994--Correspondence--January-April (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - 1994--Correspondence--May-December (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - 1995-1996--Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 6)
- NAADAC Foundation - Board Meetings (Box 99-100)
  - 1992--Foundation Board meeting--1 February (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - 1992--Foundation Board meeting--10 June (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - 1993--NERF Executive Committee meeting--7 February (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - 1993--Foundation Board meeting--1 July (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - 1994--Foundation Board meeting--28 February (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - 1994--Foundation Board meeting--14 July (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - 1995--Foundation Board meeting--28 February (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - 1995--Foundation Board meeting--6 July (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - 1996--Foundation Board meeting--1 March (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - 1996--Foundation Board meeting--25 July (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - 1996--Foundation Planning meeting--20 September (Box 100, Folder 6)
- NAADAC Foundation - Curriculum Committee (Box 100)
  - 1994-1997--Curriculum Committee (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - 1995-1996--Curriculum Committee--School curricula (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - 1997--Curriculum Committee--Archives Committee (Box 100, Folder 9)
- NAADAC Foundation - Grants (Box 100)
  - 1993-1994--Foundation grant recipients (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - 1995-1996--Foundation grant recipients (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - 1996--Foundation grant application--Faye Buffaloe (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - 1995--Possible outside grants for NAADAC Foundation (Box 100, Folder 13)
- NAADAC Foundation - Miscellaneous (Box 101)
  - 1992-1993--Salary survey letters and executive summary (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - 1993--Salary survey report (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - 1989--Financial development strategy (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - 1989--NAADAC name change--Resolution and by-laws (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - 1990--Tax exempt organization information (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - 1992--GWSAE (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - 1993-1995--Financial statements (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - 1994--Cynthia Moreno's fundraising jump (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - 1994--Focus groups (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - 1997--Cruise (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Government Relations/Public Policy Conferences - Legislative Conferences (Box 102)
  - 1987-1990-Legislative Conferences (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - 1991--Legislative Conference--3-5 February (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 1992--Legislative Conference--2-4 February (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - 1993--Legislative Conference (with NAATP)--7-9 February (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Government Relations/Public Policy Conferences - Joint Legislative Conferences (Box 102)
  - 1994--Joint Legislative Conference--27 February-1 March--Notebook materials (Box 102, Folder 5-6)
  - 1994--Joint Legislative Conference--27 February-1 March--Correspondence (1993-1994) (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - 1994--Joint Legislative Conference--27 February-1 March--Press kit (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - 1994--Joint Legislative Conference--27 February-1 March--Material for Hill packets (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - 1995--Joint Legislative Conference--26-28 February--Correspondence (1994-1995) (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - 1995--Joint Legislative Conference--26-28 February--PAC reception (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - 1995--Joint Legislative Conference--26-28 February--Scripts (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - 1995--Joint Legislative Conference--26-28 February--Speakers--Correspondence, biographies, notes (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - 1995--Joint Legislative Conference--26-28 February--Miscellaneous--Notes, schedules, bills, etc. (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Government Relations/Public Policy Conferences - Public Policy Conferences (Box 103)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--Notebook and folder material (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--Correspondence (1995-1996), schedules, rosters, position papers (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--Letter to the President (with signatures) (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--Press (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--NAADAC '95 President's Report (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--Scripts (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--Speakers' biographies (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - 1996--Public Policy Conference--3-5 March--Miscellaneous materials (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - 1997--Public Policy Conference--2-4 March--Organization biographies (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - 1997--Public Policy Conference--2-4 March--Rosters (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - 1997--Public Policy Conference--2-4 March--Scripts (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - 1997--Public Policy Conference--2-4 March--Speakers' biographies (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Government Relations/Treatment Works! - Treatment Works!--1988-1989 (Box 104)
  - 1988--Independence through Treatment Rally (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - 1989--Treatment Works (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Government Relations/Treatment Works! - Treatment Works!--1991 (Box 104-105)
  - 1991--Correspondence--January-August (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - 1991--Correspondence--September-October, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - 1991--Brochures--Drafts and final copy (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - 1991--Congressional briefing--12 September (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - 1991--Directories and rosters (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - 1991--Executive summary (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - 1991--Financial (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - 1991--Program information (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - 1991--Articles and press releases (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - 1991--Miscellaneous--Agendas, testimonies, notes, etc. (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - 1991--Participation forms and requests (Box 104, Folder 13-14)
  - 1991--Participation forms and requests (Box 105, Folder 1-2)
- Government Relations/Treatment Works! - Treatment Works!--1992 (Box 105)
  - 1992--Correspondence--October 1991-June (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - 1992--Correspondence--July-October (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - 1992--Brochures--Drafts and final copy (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - 1992--Congressional briefing--11 September (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - 1992--Directories of participants (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - 1992--Financial (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - 1992--Interest forms (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - 1992--Miscellaneous--Press releases, agendas, notes, etc. (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - 1992--Participation forms and requests (Box 105, Folder 11-12)
- Government Relations/Treatment Works! - Treatment Works!--1993 (Box 106)
  - 1993--Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - 1993--Brochures--Drafts and final copy (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - 1993--Financial (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - 1993--Miscellaneous--Articles, notes, photographs, catalogs, etc. (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - 1993--Participation forms and requests (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - 1993--Trexco (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Government Relations/Treatment Works! - Treatment Works!--1994 (Box 106)
  - 1994--Correspondence--October 1993-August (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - 1994--Brochures--Drafts and final copy (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - 1994--Financial (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - 1994--Miscellaneous--Notes, articles, press releases, statements, etc. (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - 1994--Trexco (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Government Relations/Treatment Works! - Treatment Works!--1995, No date (Box 106)
  - 1995--Treatment Works (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - n.d.--Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 13-14)
  - n.d.--Photographs (Box 106, Folder 15)
- Government Relations/General - NAADAC (Box 107)
  - NAADAC fact sheets and position papers (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - NAADAC Foundation 1992 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Communication Works group 1992 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Confidentiality 1993 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Counselor education and training 1994 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Animal research 1995 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Health care article for the Counselor 1992 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Hill meetings 1994 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Leadership mailings 1991-1992 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Legislative agenda 1992 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Committee 1993-1995 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Public affairs budget 1993 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Public relations 1992 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Public relations 1993 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - NAADAC publications (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Strategic plan 1994 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Women and Alcohol (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Frances Hamm 1991-1992 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Larry Osmonson/Cynthia Moreno 1992-1993 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Government Relations/General - Organizations (Box 107)
  - Adidas 1996 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - AFL-CIO alternative drug strategy (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - American Counseling Association 1994 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Coalition on Alcohol and Drug Dependent Women 1990 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - National Coalition on Alcohol and Other Drug Issues 1992-1994 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- Government Relations/General - Conferences (Box 108)
  - Annual conference--Chicago 1993 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Legislative conference--3-5 February 1991 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Legislative conference--2-4 February 1992 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Legislative conference--7-9 February 1993--Correspondence--June-December 1992 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Legislative conference--7-9 February 1993--Correspondence--January-May 1993 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Legislative conference--7-9 February 1993--Schedules--Drafts and final copy (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Legislative conference--7-9 February 1993--Directories and rosters (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Legislative conference--7-9 February 1993--Notes (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Legislative conference--7-9 February 1993--Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Joint legislative conference--27 February-1 March 1994--Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Joint legislative conference--27 February-1 March 1994--Schedules--Drafts and final copy (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Joint legislative conference--27 February-1 March 1994--Program (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Joint legislative conference--27 February-1 March 1994--Scripts (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Joint legislative conference--27 February-1 March 1994--Speakers--Biographies (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Joint legislative conference--27 February-1 March 1994--Notes (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Joint legislative conference--27 February-1 March 1994--Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Joint legislative conference--16-28 February 1995 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Government Relations/General - Newsletters (Box 109)
  - Legislative Alerts 1991-1995 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Alerts--State level 1995 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Alerts--Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Alert network--Fall 1993 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Alert--Contact form (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Quarterly (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Quarterly--State (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - State Legislative Chair Quarterly (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Government Relations/General - Federal Financing (Box 109)
  - Appropriations task force 1992 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Appropriations task force 1993 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Appropriations task force 1994 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Appropriations task force 1995 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Block grants--Health and Human Services 1990-1994 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Government Relations/General - Political Relations (Box 109-110)
  - Correspondence--Congressmen Rod Chandler and Ben Jones 1991-1992 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence--Hill letters from Alert members (Box 109, Folder 15-16)
  - Correspondence--NAADAC Pac 1996 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence--NAADAC Pac--Questionaires 1996 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence--NAADAC 1000 campaign 1993 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence--NAADAC 1000 campaign--28 February-13 March 1993 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence--NAADAC 1000 campaign--22-31 March 1993 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence--NAADAC 1000 campaign--April-10 May 1993 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Government Relations/General - Health Care Reform (Box 110)
  - Health care reform--Correspondence 1992-1994 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Health care reform--Proposed legislation 1992-1994 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Health care reform--Article for the Counselor (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Health care reform--Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Government Relations/General - Hearings (Box 110)
  - Oaker hearings--March 1991 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - NAADAC testimony 4 February 1992 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - SOAR hearings--May 1992 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - SOAR hearings--Statements, testimony, notes--14-15 May 1992 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - OSAP-GAO investigation (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Government Relations/General - Legislation (Box 111)
  - H. R. Bill 730 1991 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 3698--Mr. Waxman's amendment 1991 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - House resolution 8 1991 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Amendments to the Health Security Act (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Alternative bills for health care 1994 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Kerrey amendment to recission bill 1995 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Welfare reform 1995 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Government Relations/General - Miscellaneous (Box 111)
  - Alcohol advertisement 1992 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Alcohol excise tax (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Clinton/Gore plan on drugs (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Criminal justice/law enforcement treatment and prevention work group (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Mrs. Gore's office (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Miami "drug court" (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - National Counselors Day (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Proclamation (sample) (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - SOAR--Remarks of Iowa Attorney General Bonnie J. Campbell (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - State legislative advocate award 1993 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Survey 1995 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - White House briefing 19 May 1994 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Institute of Medicine (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Office of National Drug Control Policy--Correspondence (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Office of National Drug Control Policy--Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Supreme Court - South Dakota v. Elizabeth Dole, Secretary of Transportation--Brief Amici Curiae--October 1986 (Box 111, Folder 23)
- Publications (Box 112-116)
  - Bibliography (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Bibliographies (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Research Service Report (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Brochures (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - - EAP Research: An Annual of Research and Research Issues (vol. 1) - Alcohol and Your Patient (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - - Directory of Academic Institutions and Organizations: Drug, Alcohol, and Employee Assistance Program Educational Resources (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - - Alcohol Research: Meeting the Challenge (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - - Involving the Physician Through Alcohol Education and Training - Journal of Geriatric Drug Therapy (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - - Jay Lewis' Guide to Washington (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - A Body of Knowledge: Halfway House Alcoholism Programs (Box 112, Folder 7)